Guide to the New York University Archives Photograph Collection PHOTO.00001
New York University Archives
- Washington Square Campus Buildings
  - 715 - 725 Broadway (TSOA Building), 1964-1983 (Box 186, Folder 8)
    - 721 Broadway, Tisch Building, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6018; Black and White print, (Photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 6)
      Architecture.; New York University -- Washington Square Campus.; New York University -- Buildings.
    - 721-725 Broadway, New Tisch School of Arts (TSOA) Building, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6020; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 7)
      New York University -- Washington Square Campus.; New York University -- Buildings.; Architecture.
    - 721 Broadway, Warner Communications, 1981; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6022; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5x8 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 8)
    - 725 Broadway, Building Entrance, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6024; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5x8 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 9)
      New York University -- Washington Square Campus.; Architecture.; New York University -- Buildings.
    - 719-721 Broadway, Building Facade, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6026; Black and White print, (Photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 10)
      New York University -- Buildings.; New York University -- Washington Square Campus.; Architecture.
    - 725 Broadway, Looking North West, April 16, 1970; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6028; Black and White print, (Photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 11)
    - 725 Broadway, Waverly Place Street View, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6030; Black and White print, (Photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 12)
    - 721 Broadway, Unauthorized Persons Will Be Subject To Criminal Trespass (sign), undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6032; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5x8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 13)
    - 721 Broadway, Warner Communications Building, February 1981; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6034; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5x8 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 14)
    - 721 Broadway, Front of Building Window with Student Performance Poster (vertical), April 19, 1983; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6036; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5x8 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 15)
      New York University -- Buildings.; Architecture.; New York University -- Washington Square Campus.
    - 721 Broadway, Front of Building Window with Student Performance Poster (horizontal), April 19, 1983; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6038; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5x8 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 16)
    - 725 Broadway, Looking West on Washington Place, May 22, 1964; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6040; Black and White print, (Photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 17)
    - 725 Broadway, Looking North West, May 22, 1964; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6042; Black and White print, (Photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 18)
  - Brown Building
    - Brown Building, Corner of Greene and Washington Place Looking North West, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6047; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5x7 inches (Box 186, Folder 9, Item 1)
      New York University -- Buildings.; New York University. Real Estate.; New York University -- Washington Square Campus.; Architecture.
    - Brown Building, Aerial view of Corner of Greene and Washington Place from Building, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6049; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5x8 inches (Box 186, Folder 9, Item 2)
      Architecture.; New York University -- Buildings.; New York University. Real Estate.; New York University -- Washington Square Campus.
    - Brown Building, 29 Washington Place, West Side of Greene Street Looking North from Washington Place, April 1947; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6051; Black and White print, (Photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 9, Item 3)
      Architecture.; New York University -- Buildings.; New York University -- Washington Square Campus.
    - Brown Building, 29 Washington Place, West Side Corner of Greene Street Looking North From Washington Place, April 1947; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6053; Black and White print, (Photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 9, Item 4)
    - Triangle Fire Plaque on Brown Building, April 27, 1973; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6055; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5x7 inches (Box 186, Folder 9, Item 5)
    - Brown Building, Ceremony in Council Room with Mr. Frederick Brown, Mrs Frederick Brown, Dr. William H. Nichols, Vice President of the Council, and Chancellor Elmer Ellsworth Brown (left to right), April 22, 1929; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6057; Black and White print, (Photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 9, Item 6)
    - Brown Building, Corner of Greene Street, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6060; Black and White print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 9, Item 7)
    - Brown Building, seen from Greene Street and Washington Place intersection, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6062; Black and White print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 9, Item 8)
    - View of Washington Pl. from the Brown Building between Greene St. and Washington Square Place, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6064; Black and White print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 186, Folder 9, Item 9)
    - Washington Square North looking down from the Brown Bldg., undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6066; Black and White print (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 186, Folder 9, Item 10)
    - Frederick Brown Building Plaque, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6068; Black and White print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 9, Item 11)
    - Brown Building, Washington Square North, Washington Place at Greene Street, March, 26, 1984; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6071; Black and White print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 186, Folder 9, Item 12)
      Architecture.; New York University -- Washington Square Campus.; New York University -- Buildings.; New York University. Real Estate.
    - Henry James Plaque, Brown Building, March 10, 1967; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6073; Black and White print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 186, Folder 9, Item 13)
  - Brown Building - Biology and Chemistry Laboratories, 1969
    - Cell Biology Research Center New York University, Artist's Rendering, 1979; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6077; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - Brown Building Chemistry Lab, Room 553, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6079; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - Brown Building Biology Lab, Room 601, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6081; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 1, Item 3)
  - Carter Hall
    - Arthur L. Carter Hall, 10 Washington Place, Building Facade, 1987; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6083; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 187, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - Arthur L. Carter Hall, 10 Washington Place, Front Door Molding Detail, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6085; Black and White Print, (Photoraph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - Iris and B. Gerald Cantor Film Center
    - Iris and B. Gerald Cantor Film Center, Computer-Generated Rendering, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6089; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 7x5 inches (Box 187, Folder 3, Item 1)
    - Iris and B. Gerald Cantor Film Center, Looking South, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6091; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 3, Item 2)
    - Cantor Film Center Dedication with Norman F. Cantor, Alec Baldwin and Spike Lee., undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6093; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 187, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - Casa Italiana
    - Casa Italiana, Looking Southwest, Watercolor, 1990; UA_PHOTO_001_REF6140; Color Print, (Photograph), 4 1/2x6 1/2 inches (Box 187, Folder 5, Item 1)
    - Casa Italiana, Looking Southeast, Watercolor, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6142; Color Print, (Photograph), 4 1/2x6 1/2 inches (Box 187, Folder 5, Item 2)
    - Casa Italiana, Looking South, Drawing, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6144; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 3 1/2x 5 inches (Box 187, Folder 5, Item 3)
    - Casa Italiana, Looking Southwest, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6146; Color Print, (Photograph), 4x6 inches (Box 187, Folder 5, Item 4)
    - Casa Italiana, Looking South, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6148; Color Print, (Photograph), 4x6 inches (Box 187, Folder 5, Item 5)
    - Casa Italiana, Winfield Scott House National Historic Landmark Plaque, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6150; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 5, Item 6)
    - Casa Italiana, Looking Up At Windows, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6152; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 5, Item 7)
    - Casa Italiana, Auditorium, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6154; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 5, Item 8)
  - Chemistry Building, Artist's Rendering
    - Chemistry Building, Johnson and Foster, Sketch, January 26, 1970; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6157; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - Clinton Hall, Beekman and Nassau Streets
    - Clinton Hall with Carriages and Pedestrians, The First Home of the University, Sketch, April 13, 1956; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6160; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 7, Item 1)
    - Clinton Hall with Carriages and Pedestrians, Sketch, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6162; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x9 1/4 inches (Box 187, Folder 7, Item 2)
    - Clinton Hall, Sketch, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6164; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 187, Folder 7, Item 3)
  - Catholic Center
    - Catholic Center Site, Thompson Street and Washington Square South, Looking Southeast, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6095; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 4 1/2x6 1/2 inches (Box 187, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - Catholic Student Center, Looking South, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6101; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 4, Item 2)
    - Aerial View of Catholic Center, Loeb and Shimkin, Looking East, October 2, 1959; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6103; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 4, Item 3)
    - Catholic Center, Washington Square South, Looking South, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6105; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 187, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - Catholic Center, Stained Glass and Steeple, circa 1957; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6107; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 4, Item 5)
    - Catholic Center, Soup Kitchen, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6109; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 187, Folder 4, Item 6)
    - Catholic Center, Demolished For Bobst Library Site, February 1, 1952; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6111; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 4, Item 7)
    - Catholic Center, Penthouse, November 17, 1981; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6113; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 187, Folder 4, Item 8)
    - Catholic Center, Cross Installation, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6115; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 3x5 inches (Box 187, Folder 4, Item 9)
    - Site of Catholic Center, Looking Southeast, January 18, 1961; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6117; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 4, Item 10)
    - Catholic Center, Drawing, 1965; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6119; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 4 1/2x6 inches (Box 187, Folder 4, Item 11)
    - Catholic Center, Facade and Plan, Drawing, April 10, 1961; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6121; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 4, Item 12)
    - Catholic Center, Looking Southeast, Artist's Rendering, 1960; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6123; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 4, Item 13)
      New York University -- Washington Square Campus.
    - Dedication of Catholic Center, Archbishop of New York Francis Cardinal Spellman and NYU President Hester, October 15, 1964; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6125; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 4, Item 14)
    - Dedication of Catholic Center, Religious Procession In Front of Center, October 15, 1964; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6127; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 4, Item 15)
    - Dedication of Catholic Center, Religious Procession Through Streets, October 15, 1964; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6129; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 4, Item 16)
    - Dedication of Catholic Center, Archibishop of New York Francis Cardinal Spellman and NYU President Hester, October 15, 1964; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6131; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 4, Item 17)
    - Dedication of Catholic Center, Church Ceremony, October 15, 1964; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6133; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 4, Item 18)
    - Catholic Center Meeting at Gracie Mansion with Mrs. Wagner and Father O'Reilly, January 22, 1959; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6135; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 4, Item 19)
    - Catholic Center, Church Interior, circa 1957; UA_PHOTO_001_re6137; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 4, Item 20)
  - Coach Station, Corner of Fourth and Wooster Streets
    - Coach Station at Number 76 Washington Square, South Corner of Fourth and Worcester Streets, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6167; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - Coles Sports Center Artists' Rendering
    - Coles Athletic Center Original Plan, Looking Northwest, Rendering, June 7, 1973; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6169; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 9, Item 1)
    - Coles Sports Center, Birds-Eye View of Gymnasium and Facilities, Rendering, 1979; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6171; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 9, Item 2)
    - Coles Sports Center, Swimming Pool Plan, Rendering, 1979; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6174 (Box 187, Folder 9, Item 3)
    - Coles Sports Center, Bird's-Eye View of Rooftop Tennis Courts and Recreation Center, Rendering, UA_PHOTO_001_ref6175; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 9, Item 4)
    - Coles Sports Center, Site Plan, October 7, 1968; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6177; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 9, Item 5)
    - Cole Sports Center, Arena Plan (Seats Extended), October 7, 1968; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6179; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 9, Item 6)
    - Coles Sports Center, Arena Plan (Showing Track), October 7, 1968; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6181; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 9, Item 7)
    - Coles Sports Center, Plaza Level Plan, October 7, 1968; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6183; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 9, Item 8)
    - Coles Sports Center, Locker and Office Level Plan, October 7, 1968; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6185; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 9, Item 9)
    - Coles Sports Center, Gym and Pool Level Plan, October 7, 1968; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6187; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 9, Item 10)
    - Coles Sports Center, Sections Plan, October 7, 1968; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6189 (Box 187, Folder 9, Item 11)
    - Coles Sports Center, East Elevation Plan, October 7, 1968; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6190; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 9, Item 12)
    - Coles Sports Center, North Elevation Plan, October 7, 1968; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6192; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 9, Item 13)
  - Cole Sports Center Construction, 1980
    - Coles Sports Center Construction, Site Work, Looking East, Aerial View, January 28, 1980; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6195; Black and White Print, (Phtograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 11, Item 1)
    - Coles Sports Center Construction 1, Looking East, Aerial View, circa 1980; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6197; Back and White Print, (Photograph), 4 1/2x7 inches (Box 187, Folder 11, Item 2)
    - Coles Sports Center Site Construction, Foundations, Looking Southwest, circa 1980; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6199; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 187, Folder 11, Item 3)
    - Coles Sports Center Construction, Superstructure, Looking South, circa 1980; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6201; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 11, Item 4)
    - Coles Sports Center Constuction 2, Looking East, Aerial View, circa 1980; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6203; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 4 1/2x7 inches (Box 187, Folder 11, Item 5)
    - Coles Sports Center Construction, Pool, October 1980; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6205; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 187, Folder 11, Item 6)
    - Coles Sports Center Construction, Interior Construction 1, circa 1980; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6206 (Box 187, Folder 11, Item 7)
    - Coles Sports Center Construction, Interior Construction 2, September 12, 1980; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6207 (Box 187, Folder 11, Item 8)
    - Coles Sports Center Construction, Superstructure, Loking South, May 13, 1980; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6208; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 11, Item 9)
    - Coles Sports Center Construction, Interior Construction 3, September 15, 1980; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6210; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 187, Folder 11, Item 10)
    - Coles Sports Center Construction, Pool Area, January 28, 1981; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6212; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 187, Folder 11, Item 11)
    - Coles Sports Center Construction, Foundations, Loking Northeast, April 18, 1980; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6214; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 187, Folder 11, Item 12)
    - Coles Sports Center Construction, Gym Area, January 28, 1981; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6216; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 187, Folder 11, Item 13)
    - Coles Sports Center Construction, Site Work, Excavator, October 1979; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6218; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 187, Folder 11, Item 14)
    - Coles Sports Center Construction, Site Work, Looking Northeast, April 18, 1980; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6220; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 187, Folder 11, Item 15)
    - Coles Sports Center Construction, Site Work, Dump Trucks, circa 1980; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6222; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 11, Item 15)
    - Coles Sports Center Construction, Site Work, Construction Workers, April 18, 1980; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6224; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 187, Folder 11, Item 16)
    - Coles Sports Center Construction, Site Work, Looking Southwest, January 1980; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6226; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 187, Folder 11, Item 17)
    - Coles Sports Center Construction, Site Work, Excavator, Aerial View, circa 1980; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6228; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 11, Item 18)
    - Coles Sports Center, Site Work, Dump Trucks, Excavator, and Loader, Aerial View, circa 1980; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6230; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 11, Item 19)
    - Coles Sports Center, Site Work, Dump Trucks, Excavator, and Loader, Aerial View 2, circa 1980; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6232; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 11, Item 20)
    - Coles Sports Center Construction, Looking South, Aerial View, circa 1980; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6234; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 11, Item 21)
    - Coles Sports Center Construction, Foundations, Looking Northeast 2, circa 1980; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6235; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 11, Item 22)
    - Coles Sports Center Construction, Interior Construction 4, circa 1980; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6238; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 187, Folder 11, Item 23)
    - Coles Sports Center Site of, Aerial View, circa 1980; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6241; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 187, Folder 11, Item 24)
    - Construction at Mercer and Bleeker for Sports Complex, circa 1980; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6243; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 187, Folder 11, Item 25)
  - Coles Sports Center Dedication and Other Special Events
    - Coles Special Events, Two Men Shaking Hands, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6246; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 187, Folder 12, Item 1)
    - Coles Athletic Center Dedication, Jerome S. Coles Receiving Presidential Citation, November 1981; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6248; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 187, Folder 12, Item 2)
    - Dedication of Coles Sports Center, Jerome S. Coles, Kitty Carlisle and Laurence Tisch Singing, circa 1981; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6251; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 12, Item 3)
    - Dedication of Coles Sports Center, Crowd Looking at Stage, circa 1981; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6253; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 12, Item 4)
    - Dedication of Coles Sports Center, Ceremony Crowd, Aerial, circa 1981; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6255; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder data_value_missing_afff06e5b274c05662fb81d3dc6c7656, Item 5)
  - Coles Sports Center
    - Coles Front Entrance and Rooftop Tennis Courts, Looking Northwest, Aerial, circa 1987; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6260; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 188, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - Cole Sports Center, Building Plan, Artists Rendering, 1979; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6262; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 188, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - Coles Sports Center, Front Door, Looking Northwest, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6264; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 188, Folder 1, Item 3)
    - Coles Sports Center, Front Door, Sign and Students, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6266; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 188, Folder 1, Item 4)
    - Coles Sports Center, Front Door, Sign and Rooftop, Looking East, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6269; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 188, Folder 1, Item 5)
    - Coles Sports Center and Recreation, Looking Southwest, September 1981; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6271; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 188, Folder 1, Item 6)
    - School of Education Fourth Floor, Weight Lifting, December 11, 1974; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6272; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 188, Folder 1, Item 7)
    - Coles, Tennis, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6274; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 188, Folder 1, Item 8)
    - Association of Black Faculty and Administrators, Scholarship Fund Basketball Game, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6276; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 188, Folder 1, Item 9)
    - Athletics, Fitness, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6279; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 4x7 inches (Box 188, Folder 1, Item 10)
    - Coles, Fitness Room with Excercise Bikes, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6281; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 188, Folder 1, Item 11)
    - Coles Sports Center, Students on Excercise Bikes, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_6282; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 188, Folder 1, Item 12)
      New York University -- Washington Square Campus.; New York University -- Athletics
    - Coles Sports Center, Female Using Leg Press, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6284; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 188, Folder 1, Item 13)
      New York University -- Athletics; New York University -- Washington Square Campus.
    - Coles Sports Center, Male Playing Tennis, Student Handbook Cover #4, 1984-1985; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6286; Black and White Print, (Photograph) 5x7 inches (Box 188, Folder 1, Item 14)
      New York University -- Washington Square Campus.; Student activities.; New York University -- Athletics
    - Coles Sport Center, Male Beside Swimming Pool, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6288; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 188, Folder 1, Item 15)